export const questionsData = [
    {
        Question: 'Today is Monday , After 63 days it will be ?',
        Options: ['Monday', 'Wednesday', 'Friday', 'Saturday'],
        answer: 1,
    },


    {
        Question: 'It was Sunday on Jan 1, 2006. What was the day of the week Jan 1, 2010?',
        Options: ['Sunday', 'Saturday', 'Friday', 'Wednesday'],
        answer: 3,
    },


    {
        Question: 'How can we change the background color of an element?',
        Options: ['background-color', 'color', 'border', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 1,
    },


    {
        Question: 'In how many ways can CSS be written in ?',
        Options: ['1', '2', '4', '3'],
        answer: 4,
    },


    {
        Question: 'What type of CSS is generally recommended for designing large web pages ?',
        Options: ['Inline', 'Internal', 'External', 'All of the above'],
        answer: 3,
    },


    {
        Question: 'Which HTML tag is used to declare internal CSS ?',
        Options: ['gradient()', 'linear-gradient()', 'grayscale()', 'dimage()'],
        answer: 2,
    },


    {
        Question: 'Which of the following CSS property defines the different properties of all four sides of an elements border in a single declaration?',
        Options: ['border-collapse', 'border-width', 'padding', 'border'],
        answer: 2,
    },


    {
        Question: ' Which of the following CSS property sets the font size of text ?',
        Options: ['font-size', 'text-size', 'text', 'size'],
        answer: 1,
    },


    {
        Question: 'Which of the following CSS Property sets the stacking order of positioned elements?',
        Options: ['y-index', ' z-index', 'x-index', 'all of the mentioned'],
        answer: 2,
    },


    {
        Question: 'Which of the following CSS3 property can be used to allow line breaks within words?',
        Options: ['line-break', 'line-wrap', 'word-wrap', 'word-break'],
        answer: 4,
    },
]